"""Have the data for a our game"""

question_data = [
                    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Shaquille O&#039;Neal appeared in the 1997 film &quot;Space Jam&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
                    
                ]